prosperitybanktx.com 2003-12-03

# Privacy Notice

| 

This notice applies to individuals (and their legal representatives) who obtain Prosperity BankSM financial products or services on both an ongoing and occasional basis, which are to be used primarily for personal, family or household purposes. 

**WHAT WE COLLECT  
** Information we collect about you includes information you provide in:

  * Account or credit applications or under loan agreements, whether written, by telephone or electronic means

  * Credit and other consumer reports, such as your credit history or character references, and

  * Our transaction experiences with you, such as collateral, account balances or mortgage information.

**HOW WE SAFEGUARD INFORMATION  
** Furthermore, we have implemented reasonable policies, procedures and controls to help safeguard and prevent unauthorized disclosure of customer financial information and detect any such unauthorized disclosures.  Prosperity BankSM employees are trained to handle matters of utmost confidence and importance to our customers in a manner consistent with applicable law and this notice.  In addition, only employees actively engaged in the discharge of assigned duties involving customer information are authorized to access that information. 

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION  
** Prosperity Bank

SM retains our customers personal information in order to provide financial products and services and may, from time to time, provide such information to nonaffiliated third party service providers to perform services for or functions on behalf of the Bank, to effect, administer, or enforce transactions authorized by you; for example,

  * To open and administer your accounts and provide other financial services,

  * To make credit decisions and manage credit relationships,

  * To help us protect you and the Bank from financial loss,

  * Preparation  of  account statements.

Prosperity BankSM may disclose all information we collect to companies that perform marketing services for our products in accordance with applicable law.  

When we provide nonpublic personal information to nonaffiliated third party service providers for any such services that may or may not be described herein, these nonaffiliated third party service providers agree to maintain the confidentiality of such information and to use it only for the intended purposes.

Prosperity Bank

SM does not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers, except as permitted by law. 

Prosperity Bank

SM reserves the right to change this Privacy Notice, in whole or in part, by providing notice in accordance with applicable law.  

**INTERNET PRIVACY POLICY  
** When you visit our website at 

_www.prosperitybanktx.com_ , to view any pages, read product information, or use our online calculators and other tools, you do so without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information.  While we do not collect identifying information about visitors to our site, we do use software to collect information for the strict purpose of tracking activity on our site.  This allows us to better understand how many people visit us and which pages and features are most popular. The information we collect and store is:

  * The name of your internet service provider

  * The website that referred you to us (if any)

  * The date and time the pages were accessed

  * The page or pages you requested

There are instances where you may elect to provide us with personal information. For example, if you fill out one of our feedback or request forms or send e-mail, you are transmitting the information that applies to you in the form of a message. This will typically include  information like your name, mailing address, e-mail address, the kind of request you are making, and any other information necessary to fulfill your request. You only transmit personally identifying information that you enter yourself.  This information cannot be collected unless you specifically elect to send it to us.  This information is used internally only for the purpose of fulfilling the request or for contacting you directly and is not given or sold to any other business or organization. 

When you submit personally identifying information via one of our feedback or application forms, that information is also encrypted, or scrambled, by your browser before it is transmitted back to our website.  This effectively prevents anyone from intercepting and reading any personal information about you.   **Note that this encryption does not take place if you send us e-mail, but only when you use your   Web browser with one of our forms.**The Prosperity Bank

SM website is not currently targeted or marketed to children. 

**USE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU  
** Prosperity Bank

SM reserves its right to disclose financial information to nonaffiliated third party service providers to the fullest extent permitted by law. 

**QUESTIONS?  
** **PLEASE CONTACT YOUR   LOCAL BANKING CENTER.**

PROSPERITY BANKSM –  
PROSPERITY BANCSHARESSM   
APRIL 2003

_Prosperity Bank SM is chartered under the laws of the State of Texas and by state law is subject to regulatory oversight by the Texas Department of Banking.  Any consumer wishing to file a complaint against Prosperity BankSM should contact the Texas Department of Banking.

Prosperity Bank

SM also engages in the business of selling checks as an agent for a company licensed under the laws of the State of Texas and is subject to regulatory oversight by the Texas Department of Banking.  Any consumer wishing to file a complaint concerning the sale of checks activities should contact the Texas Department of Banking. 

Consumers may file complaints with the Texas Department of Banking by contacting the Department through one of the means indicated below:

 **In Person or U.S. Mail:**   Texas Department of Banking  
                                             2601 North Lamar Boulevard, Suite 300   
                                             Austin, Texas 78705-4294   
By Telephone:                  1-877-276-5544 (toll free)  
By Fax:                              1-512-475-1313  
By E-mail:                        

_[_consumer.complaints@banking.state.tx.us_](mailto:consumer.complaints@banking.state.tx.us) _  
Website:                             _[__www.banking.state.tx.us__](http://www.banking.state.tx.us/) _  
 _
